question_data = [
        {
            "category":"Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium",
            "question":"Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
            "correct_answer":"True",
            "incorrect_answers":["False"]
            },
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"DragonForce's 'Through the Fire and Flames' is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language 'Simlish' was The Sims (2000).","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"'Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater' takes place on Shadow Moses Island.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In 'Overwatch,' an allied McCree will say 'Step right up' upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies' speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"TF2: The Heavy's voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega's new flagship mascot before Sonic was.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level 'Hidden Palace Zone' was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
        ]
